<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.1.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://martinojones.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://martinojones.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2016-06-26T11:14:32-04:00</updated><id>https://martinojones.com/</id><title>Martino Jones</title><subtitle>This is my personal blog where I talk about projects I&#39;m working on and other technology related things.</subtitle><entry><title>Found Xbox One Games On My Windows 10 Machine</title><link href="https://martinojones.com/found-xbox-games-on-my-windows-10-machine/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Found Xbox One Games On My Windows 10 Machine" /><published>2016-06-24T20:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-06-24T20:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://martinojones.com/found-xbox-games-on-my-windows-10-machine</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://martinojones.com/found-xbox-games-on-my-windows-10-machine/">&lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/Qmbm5NyHGYpoz1t3dkA2hX6coA7bNX2LuNYNxw3HVJEFc4&quot; alt=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/Qmbm5NyHGYpoz1t3dkA2hX6coA7bNX2LuNYNxw3HVJEFc4&quot;&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt; Windows Insiders Program&lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    I decided to join my main computer into the Windows Insiders program so that I could see what new features and UI we will be getting with the Red Stone build that will be coming out next month. I could have just waited a month but, I wanted it now. After joining my machine to the Insider Program I had so many problems that I had to do a clean reinstall… Explorer would freeze and lockup the system and I couldn’t do anything after logging in, maybe I’ll write about that sometime.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt;Windows Store&lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    I looked around the system and wanted to see the new store too. So, I opened up the store app and looked at the new layout and the additional settings for a while. Then I looked in the “My Library” section… to my surprise I found some Xbox One games that I had purchased. All, except Battlefield 4, are digital, so my entire selection shows up.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt;PC Gaming&lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    This was great news because the PC is supposed to get Xbox exclusives from here on, maybe they’ll bring the back catalog too. Not all my games are compatible with my device, as you’ll see in the screenshots below; however, I can see those purchases. I can’t install any of the games at this time, I get an error when I try, but it’s cool to see the support PC gaming will be getting. This makes my favorite platform that much better. Hopefully it will not be like Games for Windows… that was tragic.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmWnXddvxHeuBCd1NuA1eXE2UrcY9tbhc5tSSyJZbQ6hL9&quot; alt=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmWnXddvxHeuBCd1NuA1eXE2UrcY9tbhc5tSSyJZbQ6hL9&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmPwQx9Yq2VFhJcmH8PvbRoNuNG7Uvtg88Ne2564j2RT9x&quot; alt=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmPwQx9Yq2VFhJcmH8PvbRoNuNG7Uvtg88Ne2564j2RT9x&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmQr1uyTg4Ab8EbpA8UCoHBamumy3NfBRcrr87rqbwgJC6&quot; alt=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmQr1uyTg4Ab8EbpA8UCoHBamumy3NfBRcrr87rqbwgJC6&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmaMWcigHHz1WjohvphRVDSPs9inFcBAX2QSLrS78V8NBd&quot; alt=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmaMWcigHHz1WjohvphRVDSPs9inFcBAX2QSLrS78V8NBd&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmScqFK5YnYbdKfjSn598AWPxUvv7Ahd8SQME3TVL4PusY&quot; alt=&quot;https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmScqFK5YnYbdKfjSn598AWPxUvv7Ahd8SQME3TVL4PusY&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;</content><category term="windows10" /><category term="xbox" /><category term="games" /><summary>Joined the Windows 10 Insider Program and found my Xbox One games in the store!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="<img src="https://ipfs.io/ipfs/Qmbm5NyHGYpoz1t3dkA2hX6coA7bNX2LuNYNxw3HVJEFc4" alt="https://ipfs.io/ipfs/Qmbm5NyHGYpoz1t3dkA2hX6coA7bNX2LuNYNxw3HVJEFc4">" /></entry><entry><title>Ubuntu 16.04 (Linux) Saved My Dell Venue Pro 7130</title><link href="https://martinojones.com/ubuntu-linux-saved-my-dell-venue-pro/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ubuntu 16.04 (Linux) Saved My Dell Venue Pro 7130" /><published>2016-04-20T20:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-04-20T20:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://martinojones.com/ubuntu-linux-saved-my-dell-venue-pro</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://martinojones.com/ubuntu-linux-saved-my-dell-venue-pro/">&lt;img src=&quot;https://i1.wp.com/www.lemondedestuts.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/Concept-art-ubuntu-16.04-2.jpg?resize=900%2C381&quot; alt=&quot;http://www.lemondedestuts.org/&quot;&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt; What Was Wrong? &lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    I have this Dell Venue Pro 7130, it&#39;s not all that new but, it has some nice specs. The problem is the drive... it&#39;s an early version of eMMC and you can tell. It had Windows 10 installed, before that it had 8.1.
    Both ran like crap. The OS would run fine, then all of a sudden the entire thing would become unresponsive. It&#39;s not that it couldn&#39;t run the software I was trying to run, it has 8GB of RAM and an i5 CPU. It could run the OS and
    some VMs. But it would still freeze for 1min-3mins. I just lived with it for a while. Then I remembered Ubuntu 16.04 was coming out and I wanted to try that. I&#39;ve used Linux and Windows since high school. I prefer Fedora but, I don&#39;t mine Ubuntu since it was my first Linux distro.
    I make fun of people sometimes for using it but, it&#39;s all in fun. So I held out until the final release.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt; The Install &lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    With this thing being some special build from Dell, it&#39;s a laptop/tablet hybrid, I didn&#39;t think it would work very well. Yeah, Linux has come a long way and hardware support isn&#39;t too much of an issue but, it&#39;s such a niche device I didn&#39;t think
    Linux would really run on it, or at least have a bunch of issues. It didn&#39;t, well, it had one issue. The wireless would stop working if you made the computer go to sleep and bring it back up. That&#39;s not much of a problem for me, I hibernate the thing.
    I don&#39;t like putting my laptop to sleep, it kills battery. These things aren&#39;t like tablets, their sleep isn&#39;t as good. So, that&#39;s not even an issue for me. When I started the live environment up in Ubuntu 16.04 it ran great, and looked amazing.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt; It Runs Better In Linux &lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    After I installed Ubuntu 16.04 I was waiting to run into the same issues I had on Windows, or some other bugs I didn&#39;t see when I ran it in the live environment... I didn&#39;t. Other than the wireless issue when resuming from sleep I mentioned earlier
    it has been great. Again, I don&#39;t even run into the problem because I have the system setup to hibernate when closing the lid. It runs so fast that I don&#39;t even notice it resuming from hibernation. It&#39;s a slower eMMC; however, it runs as if it&#39;s an
    SSD. The display is also amazing. Yeah, Windows could do the 1080p but, this looks great. The UI looks amazing on this screen. I know that&#39;s all personal opinion but, I showed others in my house and they agreed. I&#39;m not a big fan of Unity but, this looks good.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt; What I Installed &lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    After installing Ubuntu 16.04 I installed Numix, love this GTK theme. I also installed:

    &lt;li&gt;Unity Tweak Tool&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Nylas N1&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Google Chrome&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;GNOME Boxes&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Atom&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;FFmpeg&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Eclipse&lt;/li&gt;


    and a bunch of other things.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    So far I really like this build of Ubuntu. Specifically running on this computer. I no longer run into the freezing issues I did on Windows, and it looks and runs amazingly. I can run my VMs, work on programming/scripting projects, work on my website and lots of other things. The battery life is great, that&#39;s also because it has two batteries. If you have this thing, or any older machine really, that runs poorly in Windows I would suggest giving Ubuntu 16.04 a try.
  &lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="ubuntu" /><category term="linux" /><category term="dell" /><category term="venue" /><category term="7130" /><category term="pro" /><summary></summary></entry><entry><title>I like The HTC 10 Because It’s Just A Phone</title><link href="https://martinojones.com/00-00-i-like-the-htc-10/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I like The HTC 10 Because It&#39;s Just A Phone" /><published>2016-04-13T20:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-04-13T20:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://martinojones.com/00-00-i-like-the-htc-10</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://martinojones.com/00-00-i-like-the-htc-10/">&lt;body&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.androidheadlines.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/HTC-10-Renders-KK-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Division&quot;&gt;
  &lt;h1&gt; Specs &lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot; data-lang=&quot;text&quot;&gt;    BODY	Dimensions	145.9 x 71.9 x 9 mm (5.74 x 2.83 x 0.35 in)
    Weight	161 g (5.68 oz)
    SIM	Single SIM (Nano-SIM) or Dual SIM (Nano-SIM, dual stand-by)
    DISPLAY	Type	Super LCD5 capacitive touchscreen, 16M colors
    Size	5.2 inches (~71.1% screen-to-body ratio)
    Resolution	1440 x 2560 pixels (~565 ppi pixel density)
    Multitouch	Yes
    Protection	Corning Gorilla Glass 4
     	- HTC Sense UI
    PLATFORM	OS	Android OS, v6.0.1 (Marshmallow)
    Chipset	Qualcomm MSM8996 Snapdragon 820
    CPU	Dual-core 2.15 GHz Kryo &amp;amp; dual-core 1.6 GHz Kryo
    GPU	Adreno 530
    MEMORY	Card slot	microSD, up to 200 GB (dedicated slot)
    Internal	32/64 GB, 4 GB RAM
    CAMERA	Primary	12 MP, f/1.8, 26mm, OIS, laser autofocus, dual-LED (dual tone) flash
    Features	1/2.3&#39;&#39; sensor size, 1.55µm pixel size, geo-tagging, touch focus, face detection, HDR, panorama
    Video	2160p@30fps, 1080p@60fps, 720p@120fps, HDR, stereo sound rec.
    Secondary	5 MP, f/1.8, 23mm, OIS, autofocus, 1.34 µm pixel size, 1080p, HDR
    SOUND	Alert types	Vibration; MP3, WAV ringtones
    Loudspeaker	Yes, dual speakers
    3.5mm jack	Yes
     	- Hi-Res audio
    COMMS	WLAN	Wi-Fi 802.11 a/b/g/n/ac, dual-band, Wi-Fi Direct, DLNA, hotspot
    Bluetooth	v4.2, A2DP, apt-X
    GPS	Yes, with A-GPS, GLONASS/ BDS (region dependent)
    NFC	Yes
    Radio	No
    USB	v3.1, Type-C 1.0 reversible connector
    FEATURES	Sensors	Fingerprint, accelerometer, gyro, proximity, compass
    Messaging	SMS (threaded view), MMS, Email, Push Email
    Browser	HTML5
    Java	No
     	- Fast battery charging: 50% in 30 min (Quick Charge 3.0)
    - Google Drive (100 GB cloud storage)
    - Active noise cancellation with dedicated mic
    - XviD/MP4/H.264/WMV player
    - MP3/eAAC+/WMA/WAV/FLAC player
    - Document editor
    - Photo/video editor
    BATTERY	 	Non-removable Li-Ion 3000 mAh battery
    Stand-by	Up to 456 h (3G)
    Talk time	Up to 27 h (3G)
    MISC	Colors	Carbon Gray, Topaz Gold, Glacier Silver
    Price group	9/10
    &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt; It&#39;s Nothing Special &lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    After looking at the specs, and a lot of the reviews, you might be thinking that it&#39;s just a phone compared to the Galaxy S7, LG G5, Nexus 6P and many other flagship phones on the market; however, I like that.
    I like the fact that this phone is giving me the specs of a lot of the flagship phones but, without anything else. It doesn&#39;t have all the different apps installed like other phones on the market, as a matter of fact they
    even removed duplicate apps. If Google had an app, they pretty much just used Google&#39;s app instead of making their own... for the most part. They still have a few apps, like the launcher but, it&#39;s really minimal. As a matter of fact, the launcher is skinned to look like stock Android.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    This phone doesn&#39;t have modular-like features, liquid cooling, or stock Android from Google that will get updates before everyone else. I&#39;m okay with that. I don&#39;t think I&#39;ll be missing anything for the most part. I have a Nexus 9 and it&#39;s giving me a pretty good experience, except when it heats up and lags... something I HATE about Android devices.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt; My Current Phone &lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    My current phone is an iPhone 6s. I love this thing. It has really good battery life, and smooth. I don&#39;t get the heat and lag issues I get with most Android devices I&#39;ve used. But I miss Android. It gives me the freedom I like. I like Linux, and this gives me a very close experience; however, I wish Google didn&#39;t use Java (although they are rumored to be looking at Swift). I switch back and forth between Android and iOS devices, and I like both.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt; So Why?? &lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    I really like stock Android. I don&#39;t like seeing a bunch of crap installed on my Android phone, I&#39;ll do that :-D. So I like when I can get a clean phone, or the ability to remove all the bloat. Why? Because all that bloat is eating RAM, CPU and battery.
    Your phone isn&#39;t going to last as long because it&#39;s too buys running crap software. Also, a lot of that software is built into the Android image, so the only way it&#39;s going to be updated is if they update the phone... and we all know how often our phones
    get updated. Well, HTC does tend to update their phones, they even have a page when you can see the progress up the updates for your phone.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    I also REALLY like the build. Yeah, it&#39;s nothing revolutionary, but I still love the design of the phone; always liked HTC phone design. The phone just feels artful. I&#39;m not looking for a 10-core CPU and apps for everything I could possibly need. I like a bare phone so
    I can add what I want. Yeah, I can go with a Nexus device, but I also don&#39;t want to spend that money upfront. I&#39;m on T-Mobile, so I get upgrades more often than most with the JUMP! program. I know that&#39;s kind of a weak argument, but I&#39;m more interested in the HTC than the
    6P. The 6P is nice, and was going to be my next phone; however, I&#39;ve been an HTC fan for years. My first HTC phone was an HTC Windows 6.5 phone on Sprint. I&#39;m trying to not let my “fanboy” get in the way with this decision, but it&#39;s such a nice phone and offers me a very close to
    stock Android experience, while also not requiring me to pay ~$500.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt; Never Again Galaxy &lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    Well, I won&#39;t say never, just not for a long time. I had two Samsung Galaxy devices (S6, Galaxy Nexus) and they have all been bad experiences. I had the S7 as my first Samsung device and it had heating issues. The phone just sucked and I could barley get through
    the day with light usage, unlike the iPhone 6 that got me through the day with no problem. The S6 also had heat issues, it would even get hot when I was walking around the house, and I have great signal in my house, even then I would connect to WiFi. I would also get lag
    to the point of annoyances, especially because how much the phone costs. Updates would also be too slow for me, it seemed like Samsung would move on from their devices quickly.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    This phone is also a great example of my problem with non-Nexus devices, it was loaded with crap.
    I didn&#39;t need all the crap they installed on the phone, and it was eating up SO much of the RAM. They phone had 3GB of RAM and the phone would use 2GB of the RAM... not with my apps installed. That&#39;s crazy, that&#39;s more RAM usage than Windows. I don&#39;t want to touch another Samsung
    device for a long time. The LG G5 has battery issues, from looking at my best friend who has one, and my girlfriend has one and is seeing the same issues. So, I think the HTC 10 is the right choice for me.
  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;</content><category term="smart" /><category term="phone" /><category term="htc" /><category term="10" /><category term="like" /><summary></summary></entry><entry><title>Moon Jekyll Theme</title><link href="https://martinojones.com/moon-theme/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Moon Jekyll Theme" /><published>2016-04-06T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-04-06T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://martinojones.com/moon-theme</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://martinojones.com/moon-theme/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509720/61c61058-01d6-11e6-93ab-0918515ecd56.png&quot; alt=&quot;Moon Homepage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Moon&lt;/b&gt; is a minimal, one column jekyll theme.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not a developer or designer. And I don’t add footer to show who did this theme. If you like this theme or using it, please give a &lt;strong&gt;star&lt;/strong&gt; for motivation, It makes me happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://ghbtns.com/github-btn.html?user=TaylanTatli&amp;amp;repo=Moon&amp;amp;type=star&amp;amp;count=true&amp;amp;size=large&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;160px&quot; height=&quot;30px&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;installation&quot;&gt;Installation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fork the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/TaylanTatli/Moon/fork&quot;&gt;Moon repo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Edit &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; file.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remove sample posts from &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; folder and add yours.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Edit &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;index.md&lt;/code&gt; file in &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;about&lt;/code&gt; folder.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Change repo name to &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YourUserName.github.io&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;preview&quot;&gt;Preview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;third&quot;&gt;
    
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509716/61ac6c8e-01d6-11e6-879f-8308883de790.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509716/61ac6c8e-01d6-11e6-879f-8308883de790.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509717/61ad05ae-01d6-11e6-85ae-5a817dd8763b.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509717/61ad05ae-01d6-11e6-85ae-5a817dd8763b.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509714/61a89708-01d6-11e6-8fcd-74b002a060df.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509714/61a89708-01d6-11e6-8fcd-74b002a060df.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;Screenshots of Moon Theme&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half&quot;&gt;
    
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509718/61b09a20-01d6-11e6-8da1-4202ae4d83cd.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509718/61b09a20-01d6-11e6-8da1-4202ae4d83cd.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509715/61aa9d00-01d6-11e6-81a6-c6837edf2e84.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509715/61aa9d00-01d6-11e6-81a6-c6837edf2e84.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;Moon Theme on Small Screen Size&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See a &lt;a href=&quot;http://taylantatli.github.io/Moon&quot;&gt;live version of Moon&lt;/a&gt; hosted on GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;site-setup&quot;&gt;Site Setup&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A quick checklist of the files you’ll want to edit to get up and running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;site-wide-configuration&quot;&gt;Site Wide Configuration&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; is your friend. Open it up and personalize it. Most variables are self explanatory but here’s an explanation of each if needed:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;title&quot;&gt;title&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The title of your site… shocker!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;title: My Awesome Site&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;bio&quot;&gt;bio&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The description to show on your homepage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;description&quot;&gt;description&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The description to use for meta tags and navigation menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;url&quot;&gt;url&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Used to generate absolute urls in &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;sitemap.xml&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;feed.xml&lt;/code&gt;, and for generating canonical URLs in &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;head&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;. When developing locally either comment this out or use something like &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;http://localhost:4000&lt;/code&gt; so all assets load properly. &lt;em&gt;Don’t include a trailing &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Examples:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-yaml&quot; data-lang=&quot;yaml&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;http://taylantatli.me/Moon&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;http://localhost:4000&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;//cooldude.github.io&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;readingtime&quot;&gt;reading_time&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set true to show reading time for posts. And set &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;words_per_minute&lt;/code&gt;, default is 200.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;logo&quot;&gt;logo&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your site’s logo. It will show on homepage and navigation menu. Also used for twitter meta tags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;background&quot;&gt;background&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Image for background. If you don’t set it, color will be used as a background.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;google-analytics-and-webmaster-tools&quot;&gt;Google Analytics and Webmaster Tools&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google Analytics UA and Webmaster Tool verification tags can be entered in &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt;. For more information on obtaining these meta tags check &lt;a href=&quot;http://support.google.com/webmasters/bin/answer.py?hl=en&amp;amp;answer=35179&quot;&gt;Google Webmaster Tools&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ssl.bing.com/webmaster/configure/verify/ownership&quot;&gt;Bing Webmaster Tools&lt;/a&gt; support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;mathjax&quot;&gt;MathJax&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s enabled. But if you don’t want to use it. Set it false in  &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;disqus-comments&quot;&gt;Disqus Comments&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set your disqus shortname in &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; to use comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;navigation-links&quot;&gt;Navigation Links&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To set what links appear in the top navigation edit &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_data/navigation.yml&lt;/code&gt;. Use the following format to set the URL and title for as many links as you’d like. &lt;em&gt;External links will open in a new window.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-yaml&quot; data-lang=&quot;yaml&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;Home&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;Blog&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;/blog/&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;Projects&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;/projects/&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;About&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;/about/&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;Moon&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;pi&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;http://taylantatli.me/Moon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;layouts-and-content&quot;&gt;Layouts and Content&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moon Theme use &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/penibelst/jekyll-compress-html&quot;&gt;Jekyll Compress&lt;/a&gt; to compress html output. But it can cause errors if you use “linenos” (line numbers). I suggest don’t use line numbers for codes, because it won’t look good with this theme, also i didn’t give a proper style for them. If you insist to use line numbers, just remove &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;layout: compress&lt;/code&gt; string from layouts. It will disable compressing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feature-image&quot;&gt;Feature Image&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can set feature image per post. Just add &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;feature: some link&lt;/code&gt; to your post’s front matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;feature: /assets/img/some-image.png
or
feaure: http://example.com/some-image.png
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This also will be used for twitter card:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/754514/14509719/61c5751c-01d6-11e6-8c29-ce8ccad149bf.png&quot; alt=&quot;Moon Twitter Card&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;comments&quot;&gt;Comments&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To show disqus comments for your post add &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;comments: true&lt;/code&gt; to your post’s front matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;questions&quot;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Found a bug or aren’t quite sure how something works? By all means &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/TaylanTatli/Moon/issues/new&quot;&gt;file a GitHub Issue&lt;/a&gt;. And if you make something cool with this theme feel free to let me know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;license&quot;&gt;License&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This theme is free and open source software, distributed under the MIT License. So feel free to use this Jekyll theme on your site without linking back to me or including a disclaimer.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="jekyll" /><category term="moon" /><category term="blog" /><category term="about" /><category term="theme" /><summary>Minimal, one column Jekyll theme for your blog.</summary></entry><entry><title>I Purchased A MacBook Pro and Returned It</title><link href="https://martinojones.com/00-00-i-purchased-a-macbook-pro-and-returned-it/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Purchased A MacBook Pro and Returned It" /><published>2016-03-17T20:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-03-17T20:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://martinojones.com/00-00-i-purchased-a-macbook-pro-and-returned-it</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://martinojones.com/00-00-i-purchased-a-macbook-pro-and-returned-it/">&lt;body&gt;

&lt;h1&gt; Why Would I Buy One? &lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  I was looking for a new laptop because the laptop I had was starting to give me problems. Not big problems, just enough to bother me. The laptop’s battery was starting to die faster; I’d only get ~1.5 hours. The laptop would also start getting too hot, it would become too uncomfortable when using it. The laptop was great when I got it. It has 8GB or RAM, i7 processor, Intel and GTX 610M 2GB, and a nice 250GB SSD for great performance. But it’s starting to show its age. So I wanted something new, also wanted to try this whole Mac thing out since I have an iPhone.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt; What Did I Get? &lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  I went to CowBoom, sucks that it’s closed down now. I got a pretty good deal on a MacBook Pro. I don’t remember exactly what model it was… Apple doesn’t make it easy to find for someone that’s new to the Mac world. I looked online and it wasn’t that easy to put their chart together to find mine. I just know it had 8GB of RAM, Thunderbolt, i5, 15”, Intel HD 5000, 250GB SSD. It wasn’t the newest version, but it was pretty close. It was so slim and sleek. The Retina display looked very good. I really liked the build quality, I have to say that I haven’t had something with that quality before. I don’t know if it was ~$840 nice.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt; What Did I Like? &lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  I mentioned before that I did like the build quality. Apple does such a good job with building their devices. I like the build of my iPhone and the MacBook. The laptop ran pretty fast because of the SSD and OS X runs very well on their hardware; it’s so closely married to it. The ascetics of OS X was pretty nice, I like the flat design they’re going for; although, I like material design a little better.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt; What Didn&#39;t I Like About It? &lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  The price for the specs wasn’t worth it. Yeah, the build was nice, but the specs left me wanting a lot more for what I paid. After I purchased it I went online to see what other machines I could have gotten for that price… I instantly developed buyer’s remorse. I should have just purchased a Windows machine, then if I wanted I could have just installed Linux (Fedora). The laptop struggled to play Minecraft, and my older laptop had no problem playing that; I bought the old laptop for ~$650 years ago. I didn’t buy the laptop for gaming, but it should at least be able to do something like that, at least perform better than the older laptop. The MacBook also got hot… something I found annoying with the old laptop, but this thing felt hotter because it’s metal. The old laptop had a mixture of plastic and metal.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt; So What Now? &lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  Now I’m back on my old laptop. It’s running fine for right now; plus, I can play games like Minecraft and Cities Skylines with no problem. Yeah, the battery life isn’t all that good, but worth it for the performance I have now. I will stick with this laptop until it doesn’t work anymore. I might have jumped the gun on getting a new laptop, I can wait. This laptop may not have the best battery, it may also get hot; however, I will deal with that for now. This was my first big laptop purchase, and I’m glad it’s lasted this long. It’s almost thin enough to be considered an Ultrabook. I will try disconnecting the CD/DVD drive to get more battery life because I NEVER use CD/DVD on my laptop.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="apple" /><category term="macbook" /><category term="pro" /><summary></summary></entry><entry><title>Markdown Syntax</title><link href="https://martinojones.com/markdown-syntax/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Markdown Syntax" /><published>2016-03-15T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-03-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://martinojones.com/markdown-syntax</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://martinojones.com/markdown-syntax/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;html-elements&quot;&gt;HTML Elements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements within paragraphs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;heading-1&quot;&gt;Heading 1&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;heading-2&quot;&gt;Heading 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;heading-3&quot;&gt;Heading 3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;heading-4&quot;&gt;Heading 4&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;heading-5&quot;&gt;Heading 5&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;heading-6&quot;&gt;Heading 6&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;body-text&quot;&gt;Body text&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. &lt;strong&gt;This is strong&lt;/strong&gt;. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;image-right&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mmistakes.github.io/minimal-mistakes/images/3953273590_704e3899d5_m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Smithsonian Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is emphasized&lt;/em&gt;. Donec faucibus. Nunc iaculis suscipit dui. 53 = 125. Water is H2O. Nam sit amet sem. Aliquam libero nisi, imperdiet at, tincidunt nec, gravida vehicula, nisl. The New York Times (That’s a citation). Underline.Maecenas ornare tortor. Donec sed tellus eget sapien fringilla nonummy. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTML and CSS are our tools. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus. Praesent mattis, massa quis luctus fermentum, turpis mi volutpat justo, eu volutpat enim diam eget metus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;blockquotes&quot;&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;list-types&quot;&gt;List Types&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ordered-lists&quot;&gt;Ordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item one
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item one&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item two&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item three&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;unordered-lists&quot;&gt;Unordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item one&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tables&quot;&gt;Tables&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table rules=&quot;groups&quot;&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Header1&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Header2&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Header3&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell6&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell6&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;tfoot&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Foot1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Foot2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Foot3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tfoot&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;code-snippets&quot;&gt;Code Snippets&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-css&quot; data-lang=&quot;css&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;#container&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;float&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;left&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;margin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;-240px&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;100%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;buttons&quot;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make any link standout more when applying the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.btn&lt;/code&gt; class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot; data-lang=&quot;html&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;href=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;#&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;class=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;btn btn-success&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Success Button&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;Primary Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-success&quot;&gt;Success Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-warning&quot;&gt;Warning Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-danger&quot;&gt;Danger Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-info&quot;&gt;Info Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kbd&quot;&gt;KBD&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;kbd&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tag for keyboard buttons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot; data-lang=&quot;html&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;kbd&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;W&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/kbd&amp;gt;&amp;lt;kbd&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;A&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/kbd&amp;gt;&amp;lt;kbd&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;S&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/kbd&amp;gt;&amp;lt;kbd&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;D&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/kbd&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Press &lt;kbd&gt;W&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;A&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;S&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;D&lt;/kbd&gt; to move your car. &lt;strong&gt;Midtown Maddness!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;notices&quot;&gt;Notices&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;notice&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch out!&lt;/strong&gt; You can also add notices by appending &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;.notice&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt; to a paragraph.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="markdown" /><category term="syntax" /><category term="sample" /><category term="test" /><category term="jekyll" /><summary>Just about everything you&#39;ll need to style in the theme: headings, paragraphs, blockquotes, tables, code blocks, and more.</summary></entry><entry><title>A Post with a Video</title><link href="https://martinojones.com/video-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Post with a Video" /><published>2016-03-15T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-03-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://martinojones.com/video-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://martinojones.com/video-post/">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/SU3kYxJmWuQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Video embeds are responsive and scale with the width of the main content block with the help of &lt;a href=&quot;http://fitvidsjs.com/&quot;&gt;FitVids&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not sure if this only effects Kramdown or if it’s an issue with Markdown in general. But adding YouTube video embeds causes errors when building your Jekyll site. To fix add a space between the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;iframe&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tags and remove &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;allowfullscreen&lt;/code&gt;. Example below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot; data-lang=&quot;html&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;iframe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;width=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;560&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;height=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;315&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;src=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/SU3kYxJmWuQ&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;frameborder=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;0&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/iframe&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content><category term="sample" /><category term="post" /><category term="video" /><summary>Custom written post descriptions are the way to go... if you&#39;re not lazy.</summary></entry><entry><title>My Comcast Router Blocked The Division (Mike 20240078)</title><link href="https://martinojones.com/00-00-00-my-comcast-router-blocked-the-division-beta/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Comcast Router Blocked The Division (Mike 20240078)" /><published>2016-01-28T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-01-28T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://martinojones.com/00-00-00-my-comcast-router-blocked-the-division-beta</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://martinojones.com/00-00-00-my-comcast-router-blocked-the-division-beta/">&lt;body&gt;

  &lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.division.zone/images/wallpaper/calendar-15/the-division-calendar-08-15-wallpaper-2560x1440.png&quot; alt=&quot;The Division&quot;&gt;


  &lt;h1&gt; Hhhh, Comcast &lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt; Let me start by saying this isn&#39;t the first time I&#39;ve had an issue with my Comcast router
    causing issues. As a matter of fact I had to go out mid last year to get a new wireless router
    because it was causing issues with tablets and smartphones in the house. There&#39;s been
    some news sources that posted about Android not working well with Comcast routers, but I
    even had some issues with my iPad at the time.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    The issue I ran into was the devices were getting very little bandwith, they ran
      SLOW online. I&#39;m talking ~500Kb/s slow. I ran multiple speed tests and it was
      crazy... and these things get app updates all the time... you were better off connecting
      to the mobile data network.
  &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;
        So, I went out and got a wireless router from my local Radio Shack at the time,
        yeah we still had one lol. After that all the devices were getting MUCH faster speeds,
        more than 10MB/s. But now I guess I have another issue.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h1&gt; I Got Into The Beta &lt;/h1&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;
      I was lucky enough to get into the beta for The Division on both the Xbox and PC... I really
      like what I saw at E3. I liked Destiny for a little, but it didn&#39;t give me what I wanted, so
      I hope The Division can.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h1&gt; Customer Support &lt;/h1&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;
      I looked online when this first happened and didn&#39;t see many people talking about getting that error.
      So I had to do some troubleshooting. I was getting this error on both my Xbox One and PC; however,
      when I was at my girlfriend&#39;s house it worked fine on the Xbox One... so it probably had something to do
      with my setup. I started going through their troubleshooting and talking to their support on Twitter.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;
      &lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Ubisoft&quot;&gt;@Ubisoft&lt;/a&gt; both &amp;quot;test network connection&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;test multiplayer connection&amp;quot; shows all good.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Martino Jones (@martinoj2009) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/martinoj2009/status/692718997561802753&quot;&gt;January 28, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;script async src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    But that didn&#39;t help... so I was on my own. Luckily I know how technology works ;-).
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h1&gt; Is My Setup Different? &lt;/h1&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    Looking at my Comcast provided router I could see that I have some customizations, like allowing my server through
    the router by putting it into the DMZ. I tried removing that, rebooting my Xbox One and closing down the game
    on the PC and trying again... didn&#39;t work.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    Okay, so what else did I do after getting it? I didn&#39;t want to just reset it because I wanted to know what setting
    was cauing it to have issues. So I looked around more and found that I did change the security permissions before.
    I set them to custom so that I could have higher than low but not blocking ICMP (ping) traffic, I don&#39;t know
    why you would want to block ping inside your network, I can understand blocking requests coming in (and not blocking replies)
    but I&#39;m sure there&#39;s someone.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    I changed the setting back to the default setup that came with the box, &quot;Low&quot;, and again restarting the Xbox One and
    PC... BOOM, it worked. SOOOOO, I looked at the settings I had in my settings vs. &quot;Low&quot; settings and found that
    I was blocking peer-to-peer traffic on my router. I did that because I didn&#39;t want torrent traffic going over
    the network unless they asked me first, and I could see what they were downloading.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    Maybe I&#39;m the only person that does this and has the beta, but that was intresting to see and I wanted to share
    with others just in case they ran into the same issue.
  &lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="the" /><category term="divison" /><category term="beta" /><category term="comcast" /><category term="router" /><category term="peer-to-peer" /><category term="20240078" /><summary></summary></entry><entry><title>Run Windows as a desktop enviroment under Linux</title><link href="https://martinojones.com/22-00-running-windows-as-a-desktop-enviroment-on-linux/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Run Windows as a desktop enviroment under Linux" /><published>2016-01-08T17:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-01-08T17:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://martinojones.com/22-00-running-windows-as-a-desktop-enviroment-on-linux</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://martinojones.com/22-00-running-windows-as-a-desktop-enviroment-on-linux/">&lt;body&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    In this video I show you how to setup Windows, or any OS that can run in VirtualBox, as a desktop environment under Linux; specifically Fedora Linux.
  &lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;iframe width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/AnpxFloYBOA&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;</content><category term="windows" /><category term="as" /><category term="desktop" /><category term="enviroment" /><category term="linux" /><category term="virtualbox" /><category term="virtual" /><category term="box" /><summary>In this video I show you how to setup Windows, or any OS that can run in VirtualBox, as a desktop environment under Linux; specifically Fedora Linux.</summary></entry><entry><title>Customize Your Fedora Desktop GNOME</title><link href="https://martinojones.com/03-00-Customize-Your-Fedora-Desktop-GNOME/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Customize Your Fedora Desktop GNOME" /><published>2015-12-23T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2015-12-23T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://martinojones.com/03-00-Customize-Your-Fedora-Desktop-GNOME</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://martinojones.com/03-00-Customize-Your-Fedora-Desktop-GNOME/">&lt;body&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    In this video I show you how to customize your Fedora Linux desktop and make it... well... usable, in my opinion lol.
  &lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;iframe width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/TQ68l10Fy5M&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;


&lt;/body&gt;</content><category term="customize" /><category term="fedora" /><category term="linux" /><category term="desktop" /><category term="gnome" /><category term="video" /><summary>In this video I show you how to customize your Fedora Linux desktop and make it... well... usable, in my opinion lol.</summary></entry></feed>
